[
  {"id": "baa54625-1e3c-402a-8977-ae03b4c88452", "name": "Letters", "cards" : [
    {
      "a" : "b",
      "A" : "B"
    },
    {
      "a" : "c",
      "A" : "C"
    },
    {
      "a" : "d",
      "A" : "D"
    },
    {
      "a" : "e",
      "A" : "E"
    },
    {
      "a" : "f",
      "A" : "F"
    },
    {
      "a" : "g",
      "A" : "G"
    },
    {
      "a" : "h",
      "A" : "H"
    },
    {
      "a" : "i",
      "A" : "I"
    },
    {
      "a" : "j",
      "A" : "J"
    },
    {
      "a" : "k",
      "A" : "K"
    },
    {
      "a" : "l",
      "A" : "L"
    },
    {
      "a" : "m",
      "A" : "M"
    },
    {
      "a" : "n",
      "A" : "N"
    },
    {
      "a" : "o",
      "A" : "O"
    },
    {
      "a" : "p",
      "A" : "P"
    },
    {
      "a" : "q",
      "A" : "Q"
    },
    {
      "a" : "r",
      "A" : "R"
    },
    {
      "a" : "s",
      "A" : "S"
    },
    {
      "a" : "t",
      "A" : "T"
    },
    {
      "a" : "u",
      "A" : "U"
    },
    {
      "a" : "v",
      "A" : "V"
    },
    {
      "a" : "w",
      "A" : "W"
    },
    {
      "a" : "x",
      "A" : "X"
    },
    {
      "a" : "y",
      "A" : "Y"
    },
    {
      "a" : "z",
      "A" : "Z"
    }
  ]},
  {"id": "e3c92d60-e09c-41d6-8258-6676074814a8", "name": "Consonant Blends 1", "cards" : [
    {
      "id" : "8edbd024-82a4-4480-930f-23c1be9fdcc8",
      "front" : "sl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "slip",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "0cd57f72-d247-48a6-be27-9e03fb933a23",
      "front" : "st",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "step",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "67ef775b-b3cc-4cda-9bd5-a19a58c12159",
      "front" : "sp",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "spot",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "92839080-1203-4c3c-a657-34d7195aa8bd",
      "front" : "sn",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "snap",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "1ee851f8-85eb-4c2c-93e9-8e1f51c240db",
      "front" : "sc",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "scan",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "024790bb-57af-4652-b785-fff8d3b3c1c2",
      "front" : "sw",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "swim",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "dcc41a51-e86c-484e-b7f0-d38b063060c5",
      "front" : "sk",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "skip",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "dff6b8c8-58d1-4f01-9019-283b86420538",
      "front" : "sm",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "smog",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "11aaf022-8783-484a-a1c8-b18bc293a981",
      "front" : "br",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "brag",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "a3f84db8-ff5d-4ea0-8f9c-e31d3dcba081",
      "front" : "cr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "crab",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "52b12710-5c79-4c44-9159-01f1f6c1fe4d",
      "front" : "dr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "drip",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "050e1adc-2b08-43a6-8b88-ff7d1e858065",
      "front" : "fr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "frog",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "a3b9b17a-adff-4d17-8063-487a6d29a3b3",
      "front" : "pr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "prop",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "16270179-0993-4637-8f18-c03b9c6bd230",
      "front" : "tr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "trip",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "7e371a08-9f7e-4951-8251-a2c85d25d97b",
      "front" : "gr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "grab",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "5930a640-d420-4c7b-8319-1397418dfd84",
      "front" : "scr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "scrap",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ac03165c-3e66-4a55-b406-7de1fc4b7346",
      "front" : "spr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "spring",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "02e424c0-8382-4751-b3b9-163ed85b0d91",
      "front" : "str",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "strap",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "3e2da7d6-397d-4bbc-93ae-29d92fbe5927",
      "front" : "cl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "club",
      "backType" : "text"
    }
  ]},
  {"id": "f30aeb79-b57d-450f-a5d8-4a9abaf6935a", "name": "Consonant Blends 2", "cards" : [
    {
      "id" : "1e38d41c-9e0a-4efb-b03c-44cc05a5d39a",
      "front" : "fl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "flag",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "b7dd67d9-c547-44ba-91bb-0eb9007b7fb5",
      "front" : "pl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "plan",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "d2583ecb-2bc0-4518-8f73-a413e0f6a266",
      "front" : "bl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "blob",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "c1b265a5-1dbe-4e27-9a80-c68acd3230de",
      "front" : "gl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "glad",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "af06c4d4-49af-44d6-959a-8f1b0a737fb8",
      "front" : "spl",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "splat",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "7b1b3fdf-8253-4231-befd-287c83dc6d83",
      "front" : "sk",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "ask",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "cb138b60-967f-49d8-b257-87bd9cbe6a26",
      "front" : "tw",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "twig",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "1228726c-5c6b-4cca-8dd5-21576d6ab586",
      "front" : "nd",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "land",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ab73a786-ba93-40f6-b032-d57b939c4de7",
      "front" : "nt",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "bent",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "bad17690-5a2a-4d4b-82dc-648bb1745832",
      "front" : "lt",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "belt",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "42c9e304-a617-473d-932a-4cb045fefb8f",
      "front" : "lk",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "milk",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "cb89099c-5d88-4c43-ba9f-d13dc249f36c",
      "front" : "lf",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "golf\n",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "44f8cdf6-f211-42e6-b141-8e2e0b145d59",
      "front" : "ld",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "held",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "76ca3944-095f-43bd-9df9-da372bff86f6",
      "front" : "lp",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "help",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "1fb407ea-be73-49d2-860c-d642085bb780",
      "front" : "lm",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "film",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "84a43c1a-6b7a-48a2-829e-f2bf0c7f3760",
      "front" : "lb",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "bulb",
      "backType" : "text"
    }
  ]},
  {"id": "cd5927d7-e5c6-4182-bea1-0af9f410f274", "name": "Digraphs, Trigraphs, Endings", "cards" : [
    {
      "id" : "9a7a4546-e930-4317-ab31-9ceac1f9b953",
      "front" : "sh",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "shot",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ab5f63e6-2673-4a9e-bcc0-74b0bc76dcf7",
      "front" : "ch",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "chin",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "41cee80c-9c7c-4aed-9df7-570b92214861",
      "front" : "tch",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "itch",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "2b66470d-bda3-4b19-ae7a-aa7da2ad28f6",
      "front" : "th",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "bath",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "4e7c41eb-ca04-4c0e-9b28-31a735e9ec7e",
      "front" : "wh",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "whip",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "6b19b616-e741-4277-b13c-92fd85e496ce",
      "front" : "ck",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "back",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "fac10106-0090-49ce-ba43-e845dc697a4d",
      "front" : "ff",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "sniff",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "e810befe-5617-4118-acd9-d011c8c1e3c7",
      "front" : "ss",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "grass",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "6023eacb-1d9f-4826-be43-a1a568cb60d7",
      "front" : "ll",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "bell",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "b9d2c537-e48e-440c-bfc9-aaf82661a69a",
      "front" : "gg",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "egg",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "41bde9de-043b-4398-b9ef-b8f34a114c35",
      "front" : "dd",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "add",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "27246659-8784-4d55-8d75-33ad0323d8bd",
      "front" : "nn",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "inn",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "8f92f2c5-f2c6-4c6b-a728-8e258aedd5d5",
      "front" : "tt",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "mitt",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ae5a787a-0716-4063-be89-f0f11c7ef024",
      "front" : "zz",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "buzz",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "e8dd81fc-5dce-4a57-a13b-3f56dd8e4b55",
      "front" : "qu",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "quick",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "bea9586b-c271-4692-9b48-f18a8acd94fc",
      "front" : "ing",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "king",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "9960dc34-ffd6-4114-8e31-5b4e56718712",
      "front" : "ang",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "bang\n",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ca745c45-b1a7-47a0-bad3-596c2d22dc32",
      "front" : "ength",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "length",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "f9b3fee1-f92e-4648-a21b-879a182edfed",
      "front" : "ong",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "long",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "d19e7c04-7978-425b-8d83-62e2a41127d8",
      "front" : "ung",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "lung",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "e097415e-2bbe-40d1-ab69-17d61f4c25df",
      "front" : "ink",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "pink",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "83d93320-c126-4c02-9c31-cbf783878ba5",
      "front" : "ank",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "tank",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "d143b243-b8d5-4772-9735-9d0ef50ebf4f",
      "front" : "unk",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "dunk",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "e3f59058-bc46-431c-a28b-c29f0b94d435",
      "front" : "onk",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "honk",
      "backType" : "text"
    }
  ]},
  {"id": "a21250ca-81cb-4aca-994c-8c7e24061d5d", "name": "Vowel Digraphs", "cards" : [
    {
      "id" : "52d26559-06ff-499f-819a-c9cae99080f1",
      "front" : "ee",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "beef",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "75d7d8a9-bbe4-4810-b75a-e3e425d1c808",
      "front" : "ea",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "seat",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "980cf615-356a-492e-827b-f2f9e11e1fac",
      "front" : "oo",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "soon",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "9e61b72e-af0d-438b-bae2-22979d585788",
      "front" : "ai",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "brain\n",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "37740e1b-5197-4911-ac9a-efa684b3e30a",
      "front" : "air",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "fair",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "cdfbc701-d4c7-4c49-b86e-c2ab9bd30099",
      "front" : "ay",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "day",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "c60482d3-4857-4fba-b444-03177330dece",
      "front" : "oa",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "boat",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "90f83e36-1943-4f37-9e58-c1cceeccfc0b",
      "front" : "ou",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "out\n",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "b37a5f3b-8d6c-4939-a839-60ff923c3e3f",
      "front" : "ow",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "town",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "f9100d18-1388-4299-aa9a-f2d194fb5dfa",
      "front" : "aw",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "draw",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "11a05f4f-755a-4f43-b8fb-2c9bcf13cf51",
      "front" : "au",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "launch ",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "07b5c79c-b948-4671-a415-1a36d31438f3",
      "front" : "oy",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "boy",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "8b9f8774-2435-4407-8a21-fb882c58072a",
      "front" : "oi",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "boil",
      "backType" : "text"
    }
  ]},
  {"id": "0302fb82-a2ef-4040-8403-032749283bf7", "name": "Long Vowels", "cards": [
    {
      "id" : "a6e4b390-733f-46c9-8143-1e5af704d969",
      "front" : "ie",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "chief",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "5f58a439-5076-489a-897f-f7936e2481bf",
      "front" : "ei",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "seize",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "dddfc6f5-b788-475c-997a-3835a1ddd940",
      "front" : "ey",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "key",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "e5668406-0589-4d5e-9e8d-b5536dfb86b9",
      "front" : "y",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "fly",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "7167038e-9528-45c6-9b7e-6c24e8022835",
      "front" : "ie",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "pie",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "80b671f7-3893-4be8-a8a0-4ef1db9b0764",
      "front" : "igh",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "sigh",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "db610b4d-fae2-4d85-bfee-88c1878a1f22",
      "front" : "ind",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "kind",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "419970f0-dc1e-4472-9344-fc9fc13573c0",
      "front" : "oe",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "toe",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "e8ae1c6a-9dcc-4b02-a1a5-d76f97c102ef",
      "front" : "ow",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "grow",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "7c20100d-b210-4480-9d8a-868b79b6d8eb",
      "front" : "ou",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "soul",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "d4b5fffb-e05d-4dd5-864b-65fe913af4e9",
      "front" : "old",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "gold",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "22ad9ab5-40b7-4e7c-b994-ed05dbd91179",
      "front" : "oll",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "roll",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "d1f6b9ad-5880-42e2-a5e6-4cabc8de9415",
      "front" : "ol",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "bolt",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "1f828aa1-b4dc-4c3f-942d-97b2443a13ee",
      "front" : "ue",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "true ",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ed990445-aca0-4d19-a365-07d16cfd455a",
      "front" : "ew",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "new",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "205142a0-5fd3-4f9b-a650-001877606075",
      "front" : "ui",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "fruit",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "47ff86f3-09bd-4817-ac36-bfc6d35b0fcc",
      "front" : "ou",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "group",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "dfcc0941-6089-4824-97bf-f24046d2a314",
      "front" : "eigh",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "eight",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "804fd5ab-4f76-4ef2-81d2-a7bc5f462976",
      "front" : "ei",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "vein",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "ed374eb3-4f96-42ab-b88f-3e5669256bf9",
      "front" : "ey",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "hey",
      "backType" : "text"
    }
  ]},
  {"id": "0b906284-15e0-4cdd-8566-280d39ef53ad", "name": "Other Phonics", "cards" : [
    {
      "id" : "7a2e67e7-7a9e-40cd-9cfc-38c087840178",
      "front" : "ar",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "car",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "b1d12514-3a24-48c5-8c46-c418446f6fc4",
      "front" : "er",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "fern",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "87e14da8-46ef-499c-9e6b-56f3ce097f5d",
      "front" : "ir",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "stir",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "60f43f43-da28-42a4-b575-29d55262cb2a",
      "front" : "or",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "fort",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "7e667284-dc88-4fe0-bac2-cddcd3c22f39",
      "front" : "ur",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "hurt",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "fb3c8352-7212-4783-89b4-25e42570be2f",
      "front" : "ear",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "pearl",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "f31bf2a7-8f59-46e6-b36a-7aa006fc9ef7",
      "front" : "wor",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "work",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "694a744c-335d-467c-a290-bb64cc243696",
      "front" : "war",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "warn",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "c8c5140e-faee-4035-bb38-3cda78453903",
      "front" : "ous",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "famous",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "a9689281-61ab-4abf-a5c8-7e7cd1568f96",
      "front" : "sc",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "scent",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "371cae0d-9e83-43ec-97f7-e1e4f57f2184",
      "front" : "wr",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "wrap",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "421f5b09-40d5-4fa2-a5d8-40fb9636fdbd",
      "front" : "kn",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "knee",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "b35a0301-3212-4c9f-b4fa-d7f095ef697f",
      "front" : "gn",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "gnaw",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "62c351cb-03fa-4c9d-9c8e-01831e5fd4b5",
      "front" : "ign",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "sign",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "a7d134f2-3062-4e27-b7ac-9a63354ab176",
      "front" : "ought",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "thought",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "48040b19-a58e-42f2-8399-23cdb7e5b9b3",
      "front" : "ght",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "taught",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "b2752b75-c119-4450-8b24-ed383cc82369",
      "front" : "ch",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "school",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "127f3c22-116e-4cdd-ad16-e5e58069b693",
      "front" : "ph",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "phone",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "566f0a18-bfcd-4064-a2ab-d35e3a34e056",
      "front" : "tion",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "action",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "f44cd0cb-8cea-4792-8823-1c775d242ddd",
      "front" : "sion",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "mansion",
      "backType" : "text"
    },
    {
      "id" : "06ac2413-3710-4af3-bd58-524574fac0a7",
      "front" : "ture",
      "frontType" : "text",
      "back" : "picture",
      "backType" : "text"
    }
  ]}
]